Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Photographs PHOTOS.212
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Unprocessed
  - Videos (Box 1)